American Colony Photographers
Marist Archives and Special Collections
American Colony Photographers
2.1.2.4.1.
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1364
- American Colony Photographers, 2.1.2.4.1
  - Cistus creticus, circa1910s-1920s; 20; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Linum flavum, circa1910s-1920s; 21; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Linum pubescens, circa1910s-1920s; 22; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Hollyhocks, circa1910s-1920s; 23; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Calendula aegyptiaca, circa1910s-1920s; 24; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Althaea acaulis, circa1910s-1920s; 25; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Scolymus maculates, circa1910s-1920s; 26; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Convolvulus cneorum, circa1910s-1920s; 27; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Orchid, circa1910s-1920s; 28; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Orchid, circa1910s-1920s; 29; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Ononis natrix, circa1910s-1920s; 30; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Gundelia tourneforti, circa1910s-1920s; 31; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Locust, close-up, circa1910s-1920s; 32; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Locust, close-up, circa1910s-1920s; 33; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Locust, close-up, circa1910s-1920s; 34; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Enver Pasha (center), Dhjamel Pasha with beard, circa1910s-1920s; 35; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Mosque, circa1910s-1920s; 36; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Camels on road, circa1910s-1920s; 37; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Camels on road, circa1910s-1920s; 38; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  Box 1365
- American Colony Photographers, 2.1.2.4.1
  - Rock face, circa1910s-1920s; 1; 3x4 color (Box 1365)
  - Sunset, circa1910s-1920s; 2; 3x4 color (Box 1365)
  - Panorama, circa1910s-1920s; 3; 3x4 color (Box 1365)
  - Panorama, circa1910s-1920s; 4; 3x4 color (Box 1365)